export const lvl7 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What major sporting event is hosted annually in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane International Tennis',
      'B) Australian Open',
      'C) AFL Grand Final',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane International Tennis',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What music festival occurs in Brisbane every September?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Big Day Out',
      'B) Brisbane Festival',
      'C) Splendour in the Grass',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What celebration takes place during the first week of March in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane International Film Festival',
      'B) Brisbane Fashion Festival',
      'C) Brisbane Food Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane Fashion Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What is the name of the annual fireworks event in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Riverfire',
      'B) Brisbane Glow Festival',
      'C) New Yearâ€™s Eve Fireworks',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Riverfire',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What type of cultural festival is held in Brisbane in February?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Pride Festival',
      'B) Brisbane International Film Festival',
      'C) Brisbane Writers Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane International Film Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What is the main event during the Brisbane Festival?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Theatre performances',
      'B) Art exhibitions',
      'C) Music concerts',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Theatre performances',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What festival is held in Brisbane to celebrate the city's multiculturalism?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane International Festival',
      'B) Multicultural Festival',
      'C) Brisbane Cultural Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Multicultural Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What sporting event takes place at Suncorp Stadium?`,
    answers: ['A) Rugby League matches', 'B) AFL matches', 'C) Soccer matches'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Rugby League matches',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `What event celebrates Brisbane's food and wine scene?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Food Festival',
      'B) Taste of Brisbane',
      'C) Brisbane Food and Wine Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane Food Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What popular summer event takes place in Brisbane's South Bank?`,
    answers: [
      'A) South Bank Markets',
      'B) South Bank Christmas Festival',
      'C) South Bank Food Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) South Bank Christmas Festival',
  },
];
